The story of the drivers who risked their lives and
the men that changed the sport forever.
1 is a documentary film directed by Paul Crowder.
Set in the golden era of Grand Prix Racing '1' tells the story of a generation of charismatic drivers who raced on the edge,
risking their lives during Formula 1's deadliest period, and the men who stood up and changed the sport forever.
Narrator, played by Michael Fassbender.
Self, played by Niki Lauda.
Self, played by Michael Schumacher.
Self, played by Lewis Hamilton.
Self, played by Jenson Button.
Self, played by Jackie Stewart.
1 (also known as 1: Life On The Limit) is a 2013 documentary film
directed by Paul Crowder and narrated by Michael Fassbender.
The film traces the history of Formula One auto racing from its early years, in which some seasons had multiple
fatalities, to the 1994 death of Ayrton Senna, the sport's most recent death at the time of production.
Extensive and often rare archival footage is used throughout.
The film explores themes of speed, racing, race car
driver, sports documentary, formula one (f1).